(
"ai_sub_version": "2.5.0",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 2,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 12,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"web_search_tool": "duckduckgo",
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
In a kingdom far far away
Where all nyut-nyut lives,
A sudden calamity strikes
among the nyut-nyut
who lives in harmony.
A pink giant monster has
emerged out of nowhere and
created havoc everywhere.
A lot of buildings and villages
were destroyed.
All nyut-nyut were left
hopeless
until a mysterious magical
squirrel arrived to find a
legendary weapon, the Nut
Blade.
The legend said that this
mysterious squirrel will
bring an end to this
calamity...
紅蓮華
Lyrics: LiSA / Music: 草野華余子
Gurenge
Lyrics: LiSA / Music: Kayoko Kusano
泥だらけの走馬灯に酔う
Getting drunk on a muddy flashback
こわばる心 震える手は
My stiffened heart and trembling hands
掴みたいものがある
Have something they want to grasp
それだけさ
That's all it is
夜の匂いに
In the scent of the night
空睨んでも
Even if I glare at the sky
変わっていけるのは
The only thing that can change
自分自身だけ
Is myself
それだけさ
That's all it is
強くなれる
Being able to become strong
理由を知った
I've found the reason why
僕を連れて
Take me along
進め
And move forward
どうしたって！消せない夢も 止まれない今も
No matter what! These unerased dreams, this unstoppable present
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone else's sake
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
I learned the meaning of losing after being beaten down by the world
紅蓮の華よ 咲き誇れ！
Crimson lotus flower, bloom proudly!
運命を照らして
Light up my destiny
イナビカリの雑音が耳を刺す
The noise of lightning stings my ears
戸惑う心 優しいだけじゃ
My bewildered heart, just being kind
守れないものがある
There are things I cannot protect
わかってるけど
I know that, but...
水面下で絡まる善悪 透けて見える偽善に天罰
Good and evil tangled below, heaven's punishment for seen hypocrisy
I don't need you!
逸材の花より 挑み続け咲いた一輪が美しい
More than a flower of talent, the one that bloomed while challenging is beautiful
乱暴に敷き詰められた 棘だらけの道も
The road paved with violence and thorns
本気の僕だけに現れるから
Will only appear to the serious me
乗り越えてみせるよ
I will show you I can overcome it
簡単に片付けられた 守れなかった夢も
The dreams easily discarded and unprotected
紅蓮の心臓に根を生やし
Took root in my crimson heart
この血に宿って
And dwell in this blood
音も知れず儚い
A fleeting sound, unknown
散りゆく結末
A scattering ending
無情に破れた
Heartlessly torn apart
悲鳴の風吹く
The wind of screams blows
誰かの笑う影
Someone's laughing shadow
誰かの泣き声
Someone's crying voice
誰もが幸せを願ってる
Everyone is wishing for happiness
どうしたって！消せない夢も 止まれない今も
No matter what! These unerased dreams, this unstoppable present
誰かのために強くなれるなら
If I can become strong for someone else's sake
ありがとう 悲しみよ
Thank you, sadness
世界に打ちのめされて負ける意味を知った
I learned the meaning of losing after being beaten down by the world
紅蓮の華よ 咲き誇れ！
Crimson lotus flower, bloom proudly!
運命を照らして
Light up my destiny
Oh no!
Everything is burned down.
My house and the entire village is destroyed.
What is going on?
Are you alright?
A giant monster...
...burned down my entire village with its fire breath.
That is bad.
Do you know where that monster is heading?
I think it's headed to the next village.
Don't worry.
I shall take care of it for you so it won't destroy the other village too.
In order to do that, I need to collect power by singing and music.
So please, lend me your power, oh dear villager.
Oh, I will!
ライオン
Lyrics: 菅野よう子 / Music: Gabriela Robin
Lion
Lyrics: Yoko Kanno / Music: Gabriela Robin
星を廻せ
Spin the stars,
世界の真ん中で
in the center of the world.
くしゃみすれば
If I sneeze,
どこかの森で 蝶が乱舞
butterflies dance wildly in some forest.
君が名前を 呼んだ影で佇んだ
I stood still in the shadow where you called my name.
恥ずかしいほど 遠い彼方に
So far away, it's almost embarrassing...
舐め合って
we comforted each other...
Lionは強い
Lion is strong.
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive!
まだ生きていたくなる
I want to keep on living.
星座の導きで
Guided by the constellations,
今 見つめ合った
right now, our eyes met.
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
途方に暮れて
At a total loss,
キラリ枯れてゆく
sparkling, I wither away.
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self,
私 眠らない
I will not sleep.
風は疾風(はやて)
The wind is a gale,
東へ向かうだろう
it's likely heading east.
高気圧 この星の
High pressure over this planet's...
氷河を襲う
glaciers will attack.
誘い水(さそいみず)
A sip of water,
飲んだ胸が熱い
the heart that drank it burns.
遠巻きな 物語
A distant story...
かじり合う 骨の髄まで
we gnaw at each other to the bone.
生き残りたい 生き残りたい
I want to survive, I want to survive!
まだ生きていたくなる
I want to keep on living.
星座の導きで
Guided by the constellations,
今 見つめ合った
right now, our eyes met.
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
途方に暮れて
At a total loss,
キラリ枯れてゆく
sparkling, I wither away.
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self,
私 眠らない
I will not sleep.
何しに生まれたの
What was I born for?
何しにここにいる
What am I doing here?
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
埋まらない傷
Through wounds that won't heal,
光 恐れてた
I used to fear the light.
許された命が
These forgiven lives,
今 惹かれ合った
right now, were drawn to each other.
彷徨い果てて
After wandering to the end,
君の隣で
by your side,
火照り鎮めて
I'll cool this fever.
本気の身体見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self,
私 眠らない
I will not sleep.
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
崖っぷちでいい
Even on the edge of a cliff,
君を愛してる
I love you.
目覚めたい鼓動が
This heartbeat that wants to wake up,
今 響き合った
right now, it resonated.
狂気に変えて
Changing into madness,
祈り捧ぐよ
I'll offer a prayer.
君を愛してる
I love you.
星座の導きで
Guided by the constellations...
生き残りたい
I want to survive!
まだ生きていたい
I still want to live.
君を愛してる
I love you.
本気の心見せつけるまで
Until I show you my true self,
私 眠らない
I will not sleep.
星が降る
As Stars Fall
羽のない この私が
Those of us without wings...
憧れてた あの空
...longed for that sky.
背伸びして 星を掴む
Stretching up to reach for the stars,
真似をしてみた
I tried to imitate it.
負けないで 願いさえも
Don't give up, even as our wishes...
呑み込む闇
...are swallowed by the darkness.
それでも 手探りで
Even so, by groping,
夢の欠片
the fragments of dreams,
集めに行こうよ
let's go gather them.
As I, the keeper of the legendary weapon Nut Blade, will lend you its power.
Is this the voice of the Fire Blade Priestess?
Yes, you are right.
I will lend you the power of this Nut Blade if you can prove yourself that you have the spirit to fight the pink giant monster.
Ha! Okay!
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon!
胸に刻めよ 時代のリーダー
Carve it into your heart, the leader of the era
Who?
見た目よりかは かなりクレーバー
Quite cleverer than you look
Fool!
乾いた心 すさむよりは
Rather than letting your dry heart grow desolate
Fight!
時に泣いてみれば 見えてくる
Try crying sometimes and you'll see it
明日駆けるのは
The one running towards tomorrow
紛れもなく新しい自分
Is undoubtedly a new you
誰かのためでもなく
Not for the sake of anyone else
ただもっと上を目指せ
Just aim even higher
Dragon Screamer!
(Why? I Why? I)
昇る龍のようだ
Just like a rising dragon
君の光が 呼んだ未来が
Your light, the future you called for
導き出した 僕らを
Has guided us out
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No Question!
見えているのに 遥かなゴールは
Even though it's visible, the goal is far away
見た目よりかは かなりハーダー
Quite harder than it looks
君が踏み出す 勇気を持てば
If you have the courage to take a step forward
やがて開く道が
Soon the path will open
目指すべき 場所選ぶのは
Choosing the place you should aim for
紛れもなく新しい自分
Is undoubtedly a new you
翼を手にした君は
You, who have gained wings
どんな山をも越える
Will overcome any mountain
Dragon Screamer!
(Why? I Why? I)
叫ぶ龍のようだ
Just like a screaming dragon
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow it all away
迷いとか 恐れを
Doubts and fears
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No Question!
All my way 進むぜ 駆け抜ける今
All my way, advancing, running through the present
Ride on fire, up to you... in that case
気持ちハイペースで Step up! まるで上目指す
High-paced feeling, Step up! Just aiming for the top
諦めず探し続ける 自在のレイル
Continue searching without giving up, the free rail
いつまでも変わらぬ夢 ベクトル
The dream that never changes, the vector
空に浮かぶドラゴン 誰かに伝えたい
The dragon floating in the sky, I want to tell someone
世界をこの手に
The world in my hands
Dragon Screamer!
昇る龍のようだ
Just like a rising dragon
金の光が 呼んだ未来が
The golden light, the future it called for
導き出した 僕らを
Has guided us out
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No Question!
Dragon Screamer!
叫ぶ龍のようだ
Just like a screaming dragon
銀の嵐が 吹き飛ばすんだ
The silver storm will blow it all away
迷いとか 恐れを
Doubts and fears
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No Question!
Dragon Screamer!
Dragon Fever!
No Question!
You have proven me your spirit.
I shall bestow upon you the Nut Blade.
Thank you!
I shall use this weapon to defeat the monster.
Now I have the Nut Blade, I shall continue my journey to defeat the giant pink monster.
If my hunch was right, I think...
I should go through the forest next.
Oh no! What happened to you, oh mighty dragon?
ピンクの巨獣にやられた
I was beaten by a pink giant beast.
今は力が入らん
I have no strength right now.
巣も破壊されてしまった
My nest has also been destroyed.
Oh no, that is bad!
I can help you recover if you can take me...
...straight to the giant monster in exchange.
任せておけ
Leave it to me.
おおかみは赤ずきんに恋をした
The Wolf That Fell in Love with Little Red Riding Hood
偶然からはじまる
It starts by chance,
必然の一場面
an inevitable scene...
遠くに見えたのは
Far away, what I saw
揺れる赤色
was a swaying red color.
不思議な森の奥で
Deep in the mysterious forest,
見つけた黒い影と
I found a black shadow...
何かが始まる予感
and a premonition of something starting.
怖くて逃げ出した
I ran away in fear.
「出会い」は　「終着」へ続くシナリオ
Our "encounter" is a scenario leading to the "end"...
だからわざと遠回りをした
so I took the long way around on purpose.
会いたいなんて　触れたいなんて
I don't think about wanting to meet or touch...
話したいなんて思わない
or wanting to talk to you.
かよわい君と　鋭い僕が
Fragile you and sharp me...
出会う　それが終わりさ
meeting... that is the end.
残酷だって　罵ったって　運命は変わらない
Even if you curse it as cruel, fate will not change.
ああ、どうして君が？　どうして僕が？
Ah, why are you...? Why am I...?
おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
A wolf and Little Red Riding Hood?
きっと君は今日も
Surely you will
この道を訪れる
visit this path again today.
そして僕は今日も　そっと見守るしかできない
And I can only watch over you quietly again today.
君はあの木の先で
You're hiding beyond that tree
いつも通り隠れてる
as usual.
僕は気づかぬふりしたまま　通り過ぎた
I passed by, pretending not to notice.
視線は　絡まない
Our eyes don't meet,
声は　届かない
our voices don't reach...
ため息だけが　虚しく重なる
only sighs pile up in vain.
会いたくたって　触れたくたって　話せなくたっていいから
Even if I want to meet or touch you, it's okay...
頼りない君と　ぎこちない僕が　そこにいるだけでいいんだ
as long as helpless you and awkward me are just there.
これが恋だって言わないなら　言葉なんてなくていい
If you won't say this is love, then words aren't needed.
考えたって　考えたって　エンディングは変わらない
No matter how I think about it, the ending won't change.
会いたかったんだ　触れたかったんだ
I wanted to meet you, I wanted to touch you,
話したかった　本当は
I wanted to talk, honestly.
かわいい君と　優しい僕が
An end where cute you and kind me...
出会い　結ばれるエンド
meet and are joined together.
何回だって　何回だって　神様に願ったよ
Many times, so many times, I prayed to God.
でも悲しいくらい　悲しいくらい　おおかみと赤ずきんなんだ
But sadly, so sadly, we are a wolf and Red Riding Hood.
泣いてる君を　慰めたくて　伸ばした腕が震える
Wanting to comfort crying you, my outstretched arm trembles.
愛しているよ　抱きしめたいよ　だけど、できないんだよ
I love you, I want to hold you, but... I can't.
どうあがいたって　どう願ったって　爪も牙も消えない
No matter how I struggle, my claws and fangs won't vanish.
だからただ待ってるよ　君の涙が止むまで
So I'll just wait, until your tears stop,
あの木の先で
beyond that tree...
ずっと
Forever.
Ah, here we go!
If you eat this, you can recover super quick!
感謝する
I'm grateful.
よし。完全回復だ
Good. A full recovery.
今すぐ怪獣の元へ案内しよう
I'll guide you to the monster's place right now.
Okay, let's go!
FLY HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で...
Through sweat, blood, and tears...
汗と血と涙で
With sweat, blood, and tears
光る翼で
with shining wings
今全部全部置キ去って
leave everything, everything behind now
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
飛べ FLY 高く FLY
Fly, FLY, fly high, FLY
最果ての未来へ
To the farthest reaches of the future
傷だらけの若鳥が
A young bird covered in wounds
空を睨んでる
is glaring at the sky
低空飛行する奴らが笑おうと
Even if those flying at low altitudes laugh at you
海の果てが見たい
I want to see the end of the sea
心を無にして向かい風に乗り
Empty your heart, ride the headwind
助走をつけて
Get a running start
ホップステップジャンプで
With a Hop, Step, Jump
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で光る翼が
Those wings shining with sweat, blood, and tears
君をどこへだって連れて行く
will take you anywhere you want to go
青い衝動と 本能と
Lay bare your blue impulses,
爪牙を剥き出しにして
instincts, claws and fangs
困難の旅路も 夢叶うまで
No matter how difficult the journey, until your dream comes true
何度だって
no matter how many times
飛べ FLY
Fly, FLY
高く FLY
Fly high, FLY
最果ての未来へ
To the farthest reaches of the future
ポツリ降り出した雨が翼狂わせる
The rain that suddenly started falling disturbs your wings
行く手には黒い雲
Black clouds lie ahead
今長い嵐의夜が来る
Now a long, stormy night is coming
轟く雷鳴と砕ける波濤を喝采にして
Turn the roaring thunder and crashing waves into your applause
アン ドゥ トロワで
With a Un, Deux, Trois
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
いつも胸の奥を焦がす焔が
The flame that is always burning deep in your heart
路を照らし出す灯台になる
will become a lighthouse that illuminates your path
夜明け前の光芒が 才能の華
The rays of light before dawn
咲かすから
will make the flower of your talent bloom
命尽きるまで限界を超え最高速で
Until your life runs out, exceed your limits at top speed
飛べ FLY
Fly, FLY
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
汗と血と涙で光る翼が
Those wings shining with sweat, blood, and tears
君をどこへだって連れて行く
will take you anywhere you want to go
青い衝動と 本能と
Lay bare your blue impulses,
爪牙を剥き出しにして
instincts, claws and fangs
今全部全部置キ去って
Leave everything, everything behind now
飛べ FLY HIGH!!
Fly, FLY HIGH!!
いつも胸の奥を焦がす焔が
The flame that is always burning deep in your heart
路を照らし出す灯台になる
will become a lighthouse that illuminates your path
夜明け前の光芒が 才能の華
The rays of light before dawn
咲かすから
will make the flower of your talent bloom
命尽きるまで限界を超え最高速で
Until your life runs out, exceed your limits at top speed
飛べ FLY
Fly, FLY
高く FLY
Fly high, FLY
最果ての未来へ
To the farthest reaches of the future
It's over now, evil monster!
I have the high ground!
If I love you, would you love me too?
MIR//or
Utaraku kecil dahulu
My small utterances from before
The love will last, it will
Selamanya 'ku kan peduli, right?
Forever I will care, right?
Through me...
Broken thing have I become
And you still love, respect
Truly I never had enough
Ordinary day, it seems
The clouds of a lie in the sky
Painted, coloring my paradise
The thick rain, wash away all
Luka-duka, emosi manusia
My wounds, the emotions of a human
Rapuh dan terjebak
Fragile and broken
Lara di dunia
In this world
Will I love you, like you love me too?
Utaramu lebih dahulu
Your utterances from before
The love will last, it will
Selamanya 'ku kan ada di sini
Forever I will be here
To me, enchanting have I become
And you still love, respect
Truly I will never give in
Ordinary day, it seems
The clouds of a lie in the sky
Painted, coloring my paradise
The thick rain, wash away all
Luka-duka, emosi manusia
My wounds, the emotions of a human
Rapuh dan terjebak
Fragile and broken
Lara di dunia
In this world
The rain, finally let go
Lingers on my ego
Burning light that radiates
Evaporates, the sad and lonely me
A soundless whisper, follow me
Never let go
But, hug, hug... Hug, the loneliness
How real... My tears, in this world
To me, obsessive have I become
And you still love, respect
Truly I will never give in
Ordinary, I will be
The clouds of the color of a rainbow
Started to show me my paradise
The thick rain, wash away all
Luka-duka, emosi manusia
My wounds, the emotions of a human
Rapuh dan terjebak
Fragile and broken
Lara di dunia
In this world
Hi, finally, it's so nice to meet you
I want to love you, but, for, for... For me
The thick rain, wash away all
Bersih, suka dan duka, perasaan manusia
Clean, the joy and sorrow, the feelings of a human
Dan melebur, satu warna yang bermakna
And melt, into one color that has meaning
Stop right there!
I'm here to stop you and release all the Nut-Nuts from misery!
Woah! I can't believe that we've defeated the giant monster!
It's actually this cute! Aw~
As a celebration, let's sing one more song!
ヒラヒラ 葉を散らし 月
Fluttering, leaves scattering, the moon...
夜明けが見たいって
"I want to see the dawn," it says
叫んだ 空
Screamed the sky
神様気取れ 飲めや 踊れ どっか世界を
Play God, drink and dance, somewhere in the world...
愛して壊しちゃいました
I loved and destroyed it
誰の物 誰の物 我の物 邪魔者は排除した
Whose is it? Whose is it? It's mine. Obstacles removed.
感度が何とか言ってたって エゴに捕まれて拒めないんだ
Despite what they say, I'm caught in my ego.
まだ足りない 物足りない 死にたくない
Still not enough, unsatisfied, I don't want to die
機械仕掛けの腐った声で お利口さん達が言う
With mechanical rotten voices, the good boys say...
Who's next, what for, move on, fast forward
ウンザリだよ
I'm sick of it
死んどる抱負 愛してるわ
I love dead aspirations
もう止めてよ
Stop it already
心ってモノ測ってきて 売れば幸せですか
If you measure a heart and sell it, are you happy?
造られたショーケース ほどけ出した基盤
A created showcase, the foundation starts to unravel
世界 虚ろの果て
The world at the end of emptiness
魂を一体どこに隠した
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
感夜 赫々 宵 分与
Feeling the night, brilliantly, night's allotment
雨つぶ止め 唄と舞う
Stopping the raindrops, dancing with the song
ヒバリの空
The sky of the skylark
輪廻転生 機械論 進化の論
Samsara, mechanism, theory of evolution
人が人でなくなる日に 片羽を焼こう色よ
On the day humans stop being human, let's burn our wings
泡沫は未来へ届くよう 空から空へとつなげるよう
May the bubbles reach the future, connecting sky to sky
限りなく鳴くヒバリ達を残す
Leaving behind the skylarks that cry endlessly
難点宝物 聞かせてくれたっけ
Did you let me hear those difficult treasures?
メリディア 二人のこと 愛してる
Meridia, I love the two of us
嘘でもいいから一度だけでも聞かせてよ
Even if it's a lie, let me hear it just once
どこかで どこかで 笑ってました
Somewhere, somewhere, they were laughing
今は幸せですか
Are you happy now?
置き去りのまま
Left behind as I was
届かない想い ごめん なんで言えなかったかな
Unreachable feelings; sorry, why couldn't I say it?
悲しい思い出は 風に隠した
I hid the sad memories in the wind
唄よ あなたの元へ
Song, go to where you are
雨つぶ止め 時を舞う
Stopping the raindrops, dancing through time
ヒバリの空
The sky of the skylark
ひとりでも笑って生きれるんだ
I can live on laughing, even alone
ひとりでは生きていけないんだ
But I can't live all by myself
ずっと拒んだり 愛したり
Always refusing, always loving
裏で壊して それでも誇らしく生きれるよ
Breaking it from behind, yet I can live proudly
心ってモノ測ってきて 売れば幸せですか
If you measure a heart and sell it, are you happy?
造られたショーケース もう逃げ出したくない未来
A created showcase, a future I no longer flee
手先の鍵
The key in my hands
魂を一体どこに隠した
Where on earth did you hide your soul?
感夜 赫々 宵 分与
Feeling the night, brilliantly, night's allotment
雨つぶ止め 唄と舞う
Stopping the raindrops, dancing with the song
夜明けを告げたら
When the dawn is announced
ヒバリの空
The sky of the skylark
Hi everyone!
Whoo!
Now, now, now...
How was my performance?
Do you like it?
Did you guys have fun?
And also, for celebrating my victory...
and my birthday, we have special merch!
Yes!
So here's the merch!
Whoo!
Whoa!
How cool is it?
And it's not only cool.
This year's merch was designed to be useful too.
So let's have a closer look, shall we?
First up...
Ooh!
Whoa!
It's an awesome A3 tapestry drawn by natural-sensei!
Whoa! The whole illustration just... whoa!
It looks super awesome, it looks so cool.
You can see that I'm holding my beloved... hm!
Just look at that! Warrior Risu with full dark side!
Isn't that awesome? Whoo!
Don't miss it! And also, don't forget...
you guys gotta buy it at least five, okay?
And I think let's see what we have next.
Whoo!
A super cute tumbler for everybody!
So you guys won't forget to hydrate.
You can use it to drink water...
and you can use it pretty much always.
So be sure to use it everyday, okay?
And next, we have this.
Whoa!
A smartphone ring!
Ooh!
So you can be super comfortable...
and remember me when you're holding your phone.
And it also will secure your phone in your hand.
Very very convenient.
And I think let's see the full set now!
Whoo!
Whoa!
There's so much stuff actually.
And also, don't forget...
we have the full set purchase bonus here!
So I will explain it a little bit.
For those of you who purchase the full set...
will also receive a signed foil-stamped postcard!
And for my super-Risu-ners who purchase...
the limited edition full set will receive a postcard...
autographed by none other than me!
Autographed by me!
Isn't it awesome? Whoa!
And the pre-order window is only a month.
So make sure that you don't miss it.
Oh oh oh!
Also one more thing!
Did you guys listen to my new original song, "Hoshiga Furu"?
Did you guys listen to my new original song, "Stars are Falling"?
It will be officially released after this stream...
at midnight JST. JST, okay?
On my YouTube channel! So go listen to it!
And um... who knows that later we will have MV for it?
I don't know!
And last but not least, for all of you who joined my membership...
you don't want to miss a special additional 3D performance...
in membership just right after this show has ended!
If you haven't joined my membership yet...
do not hesitate because the extra show...
is going to be mind-boggling!
What are you waiting for?
Join membership now!
Whoo!
Whoa!
Oops, um...
but I think the time is up. Oh...
And I have to continue, but yes...
I have to continue with the membership show now.
So thank you so much everyone for your support...
for this whole six years especially.
And thank you for celebrating my birthday together with me!
So... bye-bye!
Otsurisu!